

### **CONTACT ME**



+91 987.3258.203



contact@angadluthra.com



www.angadluthra.me

## **ABOUTME**

A student entrepreneur, currently running a design firm with work experience in web development, management and online journalism.

Have demonstrated interests in music instruments, pottery, robotics and creative use of IT platforms, such as Dreamweaver, Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign.

Always intrigued by and attracted to the confluence of art and technology with any opportunity to bring in creativity.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### 2015 - Current Co-Founder & Designer, Nuked Studios

I along with a friend started Nuked Studios, with the simple idea of providing exceptional responsive and mobile friendly websites to everyone.

### 2017 - Current Designer, Wheelys India

Being part of the design team for one of the most successful entrepreneurial journeys has allowed me to explore with designs while creating content for the firm.

### 2016 - Current **Head Designer, Bottlepop Ltd.**

From the pitch, to the social media content. I head the design team at Bottlepop. Bottlepop is actively launching in cities throughout the world. Bottlepop recently went live in Las Vegas, Mykonos, Dubai

### Early 2017 Intern, Addictive Media

Worked under the Senior Graphic Designer for a short period as part of our universities apprenticeship program.

# **X** AWARDS & RECOGNITION

### Karamveer Chakra and Fellowship / March 2015

Acknowledged by the International Confederation of NGO's - ICONGO in association with the United Nations – For Entrepreneurship & Technology

### Featured in Print & Web Magazine / January 2015

Inkspire - Featured in an art magazine, on behalf of Nuked Studios.

## **EDUCATION**

### 2015 - 2018 Srishti Insitute of Art, Design & Technology

Currently pursuing a degree in Graphic Design and Art Practices from the institute. I wish to further pursue a masters in the same.

### 2013 - 2015 Vasant Valley School

I graduated high school in 2015, with a percentage of 93.5 % in the CBSE Board Examinations.

# **SKILLS**

